

Gabriela Frederika Manarisip

HR GENERALIST -HR PERSONNEL MANAGEMENT NOMINEE PARTNER

- 9
- Jakarta, Indonesia
- gabrielafrederika@yahoo, co.id
- 081213331391
- in Gabriela Frederika | LinkedIn

PROFILE

I'm currently working as Senior HR Generalist in PT. Cipta Bersama Indonesia, a construction company and a subsidiary of CCCC (China Communications Construction Company) that located in Pantai Indah Kapuk, Jakarta.

I had been working in banking industry for 5 years as a HR - Personnel Management and currently I also a nominee partner in Themis Law Asia,

SKILLS

Recruitment
Talent Management
Perfomance Management
Employee Branding
KPI Development
Operational Management

Linkedin Jobstreet Oracle Microsoft Office Canva

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR HR GENERALIST

Dec 2022 - Present

PT. Cipta Bersama Indonesia - Construction Company

Coordinate, arrange, analysis, and manage HR functions and the daily operations of HR. I'm responsible for PT. Cipta Bersama Indonesia and PT. Sino Indo Kawasan Industri

- Created organization structure, company regulations, salary structure, HR procedures etc aligned with the Labor Law of Indonesia;
- Manage HR functions including, but not limited to recruitment, payroll, and employment law, employee relations, performance management.
- Work closely with Business Development Team from Indonesia and China.
- Manage and supervise a full-time team of HR and coordinate with HR team on site.
- Mediate and conflict resolution on employee issues using current policies and disciplinary actions
- Process layoffs, compensation, and severance packages
- Expatriate License Management

NOMINEE PARTNER

Jan 2022 - Present

Themis Law Asia - Legal Service

- Assisting and advice partners to enforce regulations and make sure company adheres to guidelines
- Passively working with partners in finding clients

HR & DIRECTOR'S ASSISTANT Apr 2018 - Dec 2021

PT. Path LJ Indonesia - Heavy Equipment

- Responsible for all HR related in the company
- Assisting Director in meetings and responsible for the calender

HR - PERSONNEL MANAGEMENT Aug 2013 - Mar 2018

Panin Bank Center - Banking

- Provide advice and assistance to Product Owners and Division Head on staff recruitment
- · Undertaking regular salary reviews
- Reviewing KPI for appointing permanent staffs
- Prepare, develop and implement procedures and policies on staff recruitment based on CEB
- Employer Branding with focus on employee satisfaction
- Oversees Employee Turnover and analyze reasons of leaving

EDUCATION HISTORY

Christian Krida Wacana University, Jakarta

Bachelor of Management

• Honors: cum laude (GPA: 3.85/4.0)

Non Formal Education

TLC Academy, Singapore IELTS Preparation Class (7/9) Business Management Markplus Inc, Jakarta Service Operations